はいはいはいはいはいはい
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
Dash! Dash! Prepare for combat!
ダッシュダーッシュ
戦闘準備
Prepare for combat!
Yeah, yeah.
はいはい
They've got keen eyes.
相手は目がいいよ
Don't let them catch on until
they're in our one-hit death zone!
一撃必殺エリアに入るまで
気付かれちゃだめ
There is no way they only
brought that one puny boat.
あんな小さい船一隻なわけない
Tojo, what else is out there?
東条　さらなる敵は？
There's another one 3 km behind.
Enemy 1 approaching at 200 kph.
エネミーワンの後方三キロ
毎時二百キロで接近
Enemy 2 will arrive in one minute.
エネミーツー　一分で来る
Damn pirates! Your luck ran out when
you chose to mess with the wrong ship!
海賊め　狙う相手を間違えたのが運の尽きだぜ
止まれ　止まれば殺さない
Stop! We won't kill anyone if you stop!
Dream on, dumbass!
止まるか　バーカ
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境风景独好
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
Eeny,meeny,miny,moe...
一，二，三，四...
much the same
其实都一样
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
日听   yaya
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境风景独好
日听      奶昔
神
岛
&
诸
恶
魔
Pike or shield?
Pike or shield?  負けたくはない　でも傷つけたくもない
矛 or 盾？ 不想认输 可是又不愿受伤害
Maketaku wa nai demo kizu tsuketaku mo nai
时轴      小瑾
Te ni totte tashikameteta
手に取って　確かめてた
先挑一样在手中仔细掂量
Kitto modorenain datte
きっと戻れないんだって
可是发现再要反悔为时已晚
Whose side are you on?
你选的是哪边？
翻译  TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Omoide wa kase
Don't want to know!  思い出は枷
Don't want to know!  思念是枷锁
注释   TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Atozuke no love
Don't want to know!  後付けのlove
Don't want to know!  追悔莫及的爱
后期  aoi
(Don't want to know!) Yasashisa wa ada
Don't want to know!  優しさは仇
Don't want to know!  温柔是弱点
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
压制   娜夏
広げる両手　keep balance
张开双臂保持平衡
Hirogeru ryoute keep balance
Yori takaku toberu hou he
より高く飛べる方へ
向着更高的天空振臂而飞
Mamoritai yo
守りたいよ 僕らの翼のないこの背中に背負った
唯独想保护的是.. 背负于我们那折翼的背膀之上的
Bokura no tsubasa no nai kono senaka ni seotta
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
もう　バルメはああいう連中の発見が早くて
Oh, Valmet! You were awesome
for spotting those punks so quickly!
大手柄だよ
コ　ココのためなら　地球の裏まで千里眼です
F-For you, I could see
to the ends of the earth!
Guys, there's a helicopter
in addition to Enemy 2.
みんな　エネミーツー追加
ヘリコプターだ
But jeez, what are pirates
doing with weapons like these?
それにしても
なんで海賊がこんなに兵器持ってんだろ？
She's right. I hear a helicopter.
ホントだ　ヘリの音だ
Koko, a fast, little boat
is approaching from behind.
ココ　真後ろから小さくて速い船がきた
了解　ヨナ
Roger, Jonah. That would be Enemy 3.
それはエネミースリー
Ugo, go portside.
ウゴ　左舷だ
Use an RPG on Enemy 3.
エネミースリーにRPG
Jonah, stay down until after the explosion.
ヨナ　爆発まで伏せていろ
Their main forces are Enemies 2 and 3.
本命はツーとスリーだな
They're going to have people
come up and seize the ship,
人を乗船させて制圧するつもりだ
一歩も踏み入れさせないよ
but I won't let them get a single foot onboard!
I have a visual on Enemy 2!
エネミーツーを目視で発見
It's a Denel Aviation Oryx!
デネル·エビエーション「オリックス」だ
Watch out for the 80mm rockets!
八十ミリロケットに注意　撃たせるな
Don't let it fire! Here it comes!
来るぞ
H-How is a freighter attacking us?!
な　なんで貨物船から攻撃が…
Th-They blew up our command ship!
し　司令船が吹っ飛んだ
R-Retreat! They're aiming
at us from the portside!
た　退避しろ
左弦から狙われてる
It's an RPG!
RPG
ふん　温すぎだ　賊め
You're too soft, pirate scum!
Finish them off, Lehm.
とどめだ　レーム
Later!
あばよ
H-He punched me even though I rescued him.
た　助けたっていうのに
僕を　殴ったんだ　だから…
So I...
Koko's merciless treatment
of pirates is something else.
ココの海賊への容赦のなさっぷりは特筆もんです
What are you talking about?
何言ってるの
I was being extremely kind today.
めちゃめちゃ優しいよ　今日の私は
Well, we'll be hitting port in South Africa soon.
さ　そろそろ南アフリカに上陸するよ
Africa...
アフリカ…
Is that a Cohiba?
それコヒバ？　それとも中国産？
Or was it "Made in China"?
Once I bite onto you,
俺に噛み付かれたら
you'll only get to enjoy those
fancy-dancy cigars for so long...
そうやって高い葉巻食ってられんのも　時間の問題だぜ
...Mr. Chen.
陳さんよ
Now, now, Mr. Scarecrow.
いやいや　スケアクロウさん
私にはあなたに噛み付かれる理由はないですよ
There is no reason for you to bite me.
Yeah, right, Da Xinghai Company!
You're the Da Xinghai Company's...
はいはい
大星海公司
...Executive Director Chen Guoming.
陳国明専務
You bring legit machinery to Africa
真面目な機械武器アフリカに運んで　鉱物資材を積んで帰ってきて
and go back home with loads of raw minerals.
Everyone exclaims,
"My, what an excellent company!"
「あら優秀な会社ね」って誰もが言う
But not me!
俺は違う
I can pick up on the scent of money!
分かるんだよね　金の匂い
You've got some suspicious-smellin'
money mixed in all this!
焦臭い金の匂いが混じってんだよ
You're in the weapons trade, aren't you?
武器扱ってんだろう
I don't mean to say you stink of gun oil.
なんの油くせえって言ってんじゃねえ
むしろ　そこの姉ちゃんみたいないい香りだぜ
In fact, I'd say it smells
sweet like that chick over there!
I like Americans.
アメリカ人は好きです
It's amusing how they put so much
energy into all of their jokes.
冗談にもいちいち気合が入ってて面白い
Really? Thanks, but that
wasn't supposed to be a joke.
そうかい　ありがとよ
ジョークを言ったつもりはねえが
As a side note, you should
remember that Ame--Oh, it's my cell.
じゃ　ついでにこれも覚えておいてよ
アメ…　おっと電話だ
Don't mess with America!
アメリカなめんなよ
I'm stepping out for a sec.
ちょい外すぜ
You wait here. I've still got
a bunch of questions for you!
おとなしくしてろよ
聞きてーことはまだまだある
Like your connection with Kasper Hekmatyar.
あんたらと　キャスパー·ヘクマティアルのことともな
And besides! Check this macho man out!
もっとも　見ろよ　この屈強そうな大男
He's an elite PMC operator.
精鋭PMCOだ
You'd have to get through him just to use the pot.
こいつを倒さない限り
便所にも行けねぇわけだが
Oh, Ahmad! What's up?
おうアフマッド　なんだ
Got some dirt on Koko Hekmatyar?!
I've been waiting for this!
ココ·ヘクマティアルのネタだと？
待ってだぜ
おい止まれ
Hey, stop!
What brought this on?
Need to use the restroom?
どうしたいきなり
便所か
The Ukrainian container ship Atlas...
ウクライナ船籍コンテナ
アトラス号？
...unloaded over half of its cargo
at the first port they stopped at?
第一次上陸先で荷を半分以上降ろした？
Missiles?!
ミサイル兵器？
The crook!
悪党が
Yeah, keep going.
あ　続けろ
Karen.
カレン
Karen, don't kill him. It would cause problems.
カレン　殺すな
面倒になる
Very well, Shaojiang.
分かりました　少将
Your cane.
お杖を
You have blood on your face.
顔に血がはねてるぞ
Please let me visit the powder room, Shaojiang.
化粧室に寄らせてください　少将
…で？現地部隊の長がコンテナ一個追加要求して？
And? The captain of the unit asked
for an additional container's worth?
They fulfilled the order
then and there?! For real?!
その場で応じた？　マジか
He didn't transfer her the money?
ドル振込じゃなくて　手渡しのダイヤモンド？
He gave her some diamonds on the spot?
ダイヤだと？
Diamonds, eh?
Hold it! Hey, you--!
待て　こらおい
What're you doin' covered in blood?!
何やってんだ　血まみんなってオメーはよ
That kung fu chick beat
you up? That's totally lame!
カンフー女にボコられた？
だめだめじゃんか
Where is the unit?
部隊は？
Sir, they are already in South "A."
は　一足先に南アに入国しております
The way he humiliated me shall be
offset by the success of my operation.
受けた屈辱は作戦の成功をもって相殺する
I will not tolerate failure.
失態は許されん
Kasper...
キャスパー
Kasper Hekmatyar...
キャスパー·ヘクマティアル
Doctor! Dr. Miami!
ドクター
ドクター·マイアミ
Are you there, Doctor?
いらっしゃいますか？ドクター
♪ Butterflies wet from the rain, ♪
雨に濡れた蝶
♪ O twilight butterflies! ♪
黄昏の蝶
♪ You and I-- ♪
あなたと私
Dr. Miami, please respond if you're there!
ドクター·マイアミ　いるなら返事してくださいよ
Oh, if it isn't Mokoena! You startled me.
お？なんだ　モコエナ君か　びっくりした
Huh? What's this?
Why aren't you geared up, Moko?
なんで手ブラなわけ？モコ
That's what I'm here to confirm.
ええ　そのことで確認しに来ました
This evening you suddenly declared,
"I am going mountain climbing!"
夕方になって突然　「山に登れ」とおっしゃってたので…
You truly are preparing to go...
本当に準備しちゃってますね
You can't! You have an appointment
with Koko Hekmatyar of HCLI
ダメですよ
明日　午前十時より　DIESA会場で
HCLI　ココ·ヘクマティアル様とお会いする約束です
at the DIESA Expo tomorrow at 10.
You've been looking forward to this for a year!
ちょうど一年前から　ずっと楽みにしてたじゃないですか
Oh, Koko!
おー　ココ
It must be nice to look so young when
she's actually the same age as me.
あいつ私と同じ年なのに
若く見えていいよね
I'm sorry, Koko!
すまん　ココ
え？
I can't make the appointment!
約束は守れん！
ええーっ？
If I don't go, the butterflies--! The butterflies--!
私が行かねば蝶が…
蝶々が…
I was afraid that's what she was after.
やはり目的はそうですか
Dr. Miami...
ドクター·マイアミ
Do you think she is still chasing after butterflies?
相変わらず蝶々追い掛け回してるんですかね
Probably. Her fanaticism isn't normal!
だろうね
あいつのマニア度異常だもん
She's an officer in the Worldwide
something-or-other Butterfly Group.
「国際なんとか蝶の会」とか　幹部だし
Jonah, tomorrow we'll be seeing...
明日会うわねヨナ
...Professor Minami Amada, AKA Dr. Miami.
天田南博士
ドクター·マイアミ
She's currently in South Africa
with a German toy factory,
今はドイツの玩具会社の南アフリカ工場にいるが
but she is a robotics specialist
whose stuff pretty much always
彼女の作る玩具は必ずと言っていいほど軍事転用にされてしまう
gets diverted to military affairs.
ロボット技術のスペシャリストだ
I don't care if people apply
my research to weaponry
私の研究応用して　兵器を作って殺し合おうが何にしようが
and use it to kill humans and what not.
That problem is insignificant when
compared to beautiful butterflies
そんな問題は　今にも絶滅しそうな美しい蝶と比べたら
falling on the brink of extinction.
瑣末なものだよ
After all, there are 6.6 billion of us.
六十六億もいるんだから
Humans have over-reproduced.
増えすぎだよ　人間
The mountain you have
in mind is covered in snow.
目指す山は今　雪に覆われています
Don't worry about that, Moko!
その点は心配ないモコ
Look! I've got a GPS and the thesis
見て　GPSと　国際的権威ジェームス博士の論文
by international butterfly
authority, Professor James!
This is hot news, fresh out this morning!
今朝発表されたホットなニュース
Let's put our faith in Professor James!
ジェームス博士を信じて
Who?!
誰！？
We're going to look for that rare butterfly!
幻の蝶を探しに行くよ
Be ready in five!
五分で準備して
This is a bad idea, Doctor!
まずいですよ　ドクター
While you're fussing with me,
the butterflies' lives are--! They'll die!
モコがブーブー言っている間に　蝶の命が
死ぬ
Knock it off!
そんな
You're down to four minutes! Go on!
あと四分　ほら
This is a bad idea, Doctor!
まずいですよ　ドクター
96... 97...
９６　９７
98... 99...
９８　９９
Africa...
アフリカ
Africa! Africa!
Africa! Africa! Africa! Africa!
アフリカ
アフリカ…
何度目でしたっけ？　私　アフリカ…
What number was I on with Africa?
Good morning, Jonah.
おっ　はようございます　ヨナ君
Good morning, Valmet.
おはよう　バルメ
Here. It's a rubber knife.
はい　ゴム製のナイフです
Care to join me for some morning exercises?
朝の体操をしませんか
Big swings are a no go.
おお振りはNGです
Even if it's shallow, go for several strikes.
浅くても何度も　切っていれば良いのだ
It's hot!
熱っ
Crawl close to the ground!
地面を這うように
You're screwed once you jump.
ジャンプしてはおしまい
It's an indication that I can
do whatever I want to you.
もうどうにでもしてという合図ですね
Now then, let's take
a shower before we head out.
さ　出発の前にシャワーを
What's wrong?
どうした
Well, it isn't the designated time yet...
いや　まだ約束の時間前なんだけど…
この「来る気配のなさ」はなんだろう…
But why does it feel like
she isn't going to show up?
Five dollars on her pulling a no show.
すっぽかされたに５ドル
Koko! Koko!
ココさん　ココさん
Ms. Koko Hekmatyar, I am terribly sorry!
ココ·ヘクマティアル様
申し訳ございません
Malin, long time no see.
マーリンさん　お久しぶり
It is good to see you again.
ご無沙汰しております
Actually, about Dr. Miami--
それでですね　ドクター·マイアミは…
Stop! I know what happened since you're here.
待った　あなたが来たのですべて分かったよ
"Miami went off somewhere," right?
南はどっかへ行っちゃった　でしょう
Exactly! I am truly very sorry!
そのとおりです　大変申し訳ありません
There is no need for you to apologize, Malin.
マリーンさんが謝ることじゃないよ
Also, this is an unrelated matter, but...
あの…それとは別件なのですが
うん
A mysterious Chinese man?
謎の中国人？
That's right.
そうなんですよ
An elderly man with a cane and his
young secretary often visited the Doctor.
杖をついたお年を召した男子と
若い秘書の二人組が
よくドクターのもとに…
The secretary had a piercing glare,
秘書の方が　また表情は鋭いんですけど
but her hair was silky and
she looked very charming.
髪がサラサラでとても可愛らしくて
Lately they have been taking
the Doctor out to eat at Port Elizabeth.
最近頻繁にポートエリザベスで食事されて　夜遅く帰ってこられます
She doesn't get back until late.
She says, "The fried rice was great!"
「チャーハン美味しかった」なんてドクター純粋な方なので
The doctor can be so naïve.
But she won't answer when I ask,
"What was that man like?"
でも　「あの方はどういう方なんですか」って聞いても
教えてくれないんですよ　ドクターも　モコエナも
Neither Doctor nor Mokoena will talk!
It's like they are trying not
to cause the company alarm.
まるで　会社に心配かけまいとしてるみたいで怖くて怖くて…
I'm terribly afraid for her...
あ　でも今日はチョウチョ探しに行ったみたいですよ
But apparently she went butterfly hunting today.
She e-mailed me the GPS coordinates.
GPSの座標が　私のメールアドレスに
流れて入場しちゃってるが
We kind of followed the crowd in,
but what do you think this is, Jonah?
ココは一体何だと思う？ヨナ
兵器の展示場だ
A weapons expo.
Exactly!
そのとおり
Are they all new inventions?
全部新しく作られた物？
うーん　それは少ない
Very few things are.
Local munitions makers aside,
the makers from the west bring in
地元の軍需メーカーはともかく
西側のメーカーが持ち寄るのは
upgrade packages where they have
strengthened pre-existing weapons.
もうある兵器を強化するアップグレードパッケージ
これがトレンドだ
That's the trend, but it's going to change.
でもこれからは違う
おお　これはこれはココ·ヘクマティアル
Oh, my, my! It's Koko Hekmatyar.
What a coincidence.
奇遇ですな
That sarcastic voice could only belong to
その嫌味な声は…
President Curry of England's CCAT!
イングランドCCAT社　カリー社長
あ　ココちゃんとヨナだ
It's Koko and Jonah!
Even Mildo and Lou are here.
ミルドとルーも
Did you buy Kern & Krauss Co.'s new toy?
ケルンとクラウス社の新作　買った？
Wasn't that package 200 million Euros?
あのパッケージじゃ　二億ユーロか…
--We can't move with that infestation
of U.S. Navy patrols around.
米海軍のパトロールがうじゃうじゃで　動けねぇ
--President Curry, how was this DIESA?
--We can't move with that infestation
of U.S. Navy patrols around.
カリー社長　いかがでした？
今回のDIESAは
全くお話になりませんな
It was a waste of time.
I'm going to pull out of East and
South Africa for the time being.
私は当面　東と南アフリカからは手を引きます
え
おっと　私はこれにて　ココ·ヘクマティアル
Well, you'll have to excuse me, Koko Hekmatyar.
はじめまして　ミス·ヘクマティアル
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Miss Hekmatyar.
I am Chen of the Da Xinghai
Company out of Hong Kong.
香港の　大星海公司の陳です
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
お見知りおきを
It's a pleasure, Mr. Chen.
はじめまして　ミスター陳
誠に失礼だが
I know this is terribly rude of me,
but could you spare some time for me tonight?
今日の夜少し時間いただけますかな
As you can see, my bad leg makes
it difficult to talk while standing.
ご覧のとおり足が悪くて　立ち話が困難なのです
If you are interested, I would
love to take you out to dinner.
よろしければ　食事にお招きしたいのですが
You're on if you treat me to high-end Chinese!
高級中華でしたら飛んで行きます
You're a fascinating lady.
面白い女性だ
If you'll pardon me, Miss.
それではミス　楽しみです
I'm looking forward to dinner.
Lehm?
レーム
Yep.
はいよ
A Chinese gentleman invited me out to dinner.
中国紳士にお夕食呼ばれちゃった
いいじゃん　行ってくれば？
Sounds good! Why don't you go?
Follow this memo. Get fully suited up.
このメモを　完全武装だ
Yeah, yeah.
はいはい
"The wench's unit is on the move."
Pass that on to Karen.
小娘の部隊の動きをカレンに伝えろ
Roger.
了解
No matter what you say,
eight people in one car is cramped!
いくらなんでも一台に八人はきついだろう
Plus there's our luggage!
荷物とか
We're on a snow-covered mountain.
Wrap white tape around your gun, Jonah.
雪山だ　銃に白テープ巻きなヨナ坊
Did everyone see the picture?
全員写真は見たのか
--The mission is to secure this lady, Dr. Miami.
--She looks like a space case.
ミッションは彼女
ドクター·マイアミの保護
--And if anyone tries to get in our way...
--There are a lot of scientists like that.
そして　妨害者の出現の際は
...exterminate them.
それの撃滅
I don't think there are going to
be any butterflies up ahead, Doctor.
この先に　蝶がいるとは思えないのですが　ドクター
Don't worry. Don't worry, Moko.
大丈夫大丈夫　モコ
They are way down there.
ここからずーっと下りなの
There is a butterfly paradise down there!
そこに蝶のパラダイスがあるの
なのに　鉄砲なんか持ってきて
And here you are, strapping a gun.
I need it to protect you...
あなたをお守りするのに　必要なものです
Weirdo.
変なの
さ　さっさとドクター·マイアミ捜して帰ろうぜ
Come on! Let's hurry and find
Dr. Miami so we can get back.
Lieutenant Low...
ロウ中尉
連中との距離は？
How much distance is between us?
Ma'am, about 200 meters.
は　二百ｍ
The enemy possesses submachine guns,
assault rifles, and sniper rifles.
敵の武装はサブマシンガン　アサルトライフル　スタンドライト
Dr. Minami Amada has not
reached Point Paradise as of yet.
天田南博士はまだ　ポイント「楽園」についていません
They are like normal people out mountain hiking.
一般人の山登りです
この距離の先回りを維持する　行け
We shall maintain our distance ahead of them.
Go!
Who cares what happens to Dr. Minami Amada?
天田南博士の身柄など
I'll cut their numbers
奴らを滅し
and dedicate their deaths to my subordinates,
キャスパー·ヘクマティアルに狩られた私の部下への供物にしてやる
who were killed by Kasper Hekmatyar.
How 'bout it? Think any
enemies are out there, Jonah?
どうだ？
敵がいそうか？　ヨナ坊
Don't ask that! There are eight of them.
聞かないでよね
八人もいるんだ
--I think it would be best if we
each picked up on that ourselves.
それぞれで感じたほうがいいと思う
--Ugh!
--I think it would be best if we
each picked up on that ourselves.
ウっ
「ウっ」ですって
He made you go, "Ugh!"
Lutz, you should hunker down in
the mountains and have Jonah train you!
ルツはちょっと山篭りしてヨナ君に訓練してもらうといいです
Shut it, Chief!
言うぜアネゴ
Hey, now. Keep it quiet.
おいおい　静かにしな
This isn't a fieldtrip.
遠足じゃねぇんだから
Tojo!
東条
How do you say, "Doctor," in Japanese?
ドクターって日本語でどう言うの？
Hakase.
ハカセだ
Ha-ka-se.
ハ·カ·セ
Hakase!
博士
--Hakase!
--Scatter!
博士
Hakase!
Hakase! Miami!
It's a bluff. Don't fall for it.
カマかけだ　乗るな
Hakase! Hakase!
博士
Damn it! They know where we are.
クソ　居場所気付かれてるじゃねぇか
落ち着け
Chill! He's hoping to find us by shooting blindly.
適当に撃って探ってるだけだ
Jonah, where is the enemy?
ヨナ　敵はどこだ
見えるのか
Can you see them?
I'm just trying to find them by shooting around.
適当に撃って探ってるだけだ
The fool!
間抜けが
Whoo boy! The army ants
are actually coming out!
おうおう　出てきたな　兵隊アリが
Those were some crazy tactics,
まったく　やり方はめちゃくちゃだが
but I'll give you credit for
screwing up the timing of their ambush.
奴らの待ち伏せのタイミングを崩したのは褒めてやる
お前一人のせいで
It's all your fault...
...that the plan is in shambles.
作戦が破綻したぞ
You bungled things up during
that incident with Kasper as well.
キャスパーの件もお前が綻びだったな
Apologize from Hell.
地獄で詫びてこい
Valmet?
バルメ？
Hikari yokotaeru wadatsumi
光横たえる海神
光怪陆离的海底龙神
Soukon no ma ni yurameku ayamachi
創痕の間に揺らめく過ち
累累创痕之间摇曳着缕缕罪孽
Fujou shite iki wo tsugi
浮上して息を継ぎ
浮出水面 吸清吐浊
Tokasare majiru dake no zouai wo te ni shita
溶かされ混じるだけの憎愛を手にした
爱与恨 如漆似胶 如影随形
矛盾孕む
矛盾诞世
Mujun haramu
Kono sekai goto
この世界ごと 覆い尽くしてる策動の音に傾く夢
冥冥的梦中 世界渐渐倾浸于欺言诡语之中
Ooitsukushiteru sakudou no ne ni katamuku yume
Ashi wa mou nai
脚は　もう無い
足膝 已没入虚无
Suiheki wo tsuranuku kodou
水壁を貫く鼓動
透过水壁 传来阵阵鼓动..
恶魔岛字幕组(bbs.emland.net)
诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)
African Golden Butterflies phase.2
本字幕由   恶魔岛字幕组   &   诸神字幕组   联合制作
(bbs.emland.net)    (kamigami.org)
翻译 TL旧民        日听 yaya
注释 TL旧民        日听 奶昔
后期 aoi           压制 娜夏
仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
诸神字幕组
恶魔岛字幕组
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"